(Toby:)A young boy on the cusp of manhood.
(Toby:)His only companions,
mongrel dogs and malarial mosquitoes.
(Toby:)Desperate and alone,
he reached out to a man...
(Toby:)...who promised to introduce him
to a merciful, loving God...
(Toby:)...but who instead introduced him
to a gin-pickled tongue...
(Toby:)...shoved down his adolescent throat.
(Toby:)What choice did he have...
(Toby:)...but to drink, shoot
and snort his pain away?
Don't forget genetic predisposition
towards addiction.
(Toby:)Never been proven.
- There have been studies.
- Not double-blind studies.
How could there be?
Who would be the control group?
(Leonard:)As you can see,
detoxing can get pretty ugly.
(Leonard:)- Let's give them some privacy.
- Yeah.
Do you wanna come over,
have coffee?
- Sounds good.
- I have a video of me singing last night.
Do you wanna see it?
- Gee, why wouldn't I?
- This is even better...
(Penny:)...than you coming to the showcase,
now I get to watch you watch me.